Το Plex ζήτησε 120€ για να συνεχίσετε να βλέπετε από τις συσκευές σας.
Το πλήρωσα εγώ το ποσό.
Αν χρησιμοποιείτε συχνά και μπορείτε,
οποιαδήποτε συμβολή θα εκτιμηθεί.
It's been a while, Flamme.
You're there like the wind
Closing your eyes at sunset
I wonder what's on your mind
With your eyelids open
Your eyes shone like glass
It faintly smelled like a sunny day
Clear up the sky, let flowers bloom
Bloom and blame it on the sunny sky
Even the rain, when it stops
Will make you shine in the sunlight
Calm the stirring sounds in my heart
We go like the sunny wind
Go on and fly over that cloud
Further and further away
Bargland.
The young are too hot-blooded.
The so-called privilege is nonsense.
What makes you say that?
Do you even have to ask?
The greatest joy of magic
lies in searching for it.
That's all.
I see.
Time passes quickly.
The student I chose to train on a whim
has already returned with her own student.
This is Frieren.
An elf, huh?
She's strong. I like her.
Tell me what spell you desire.
I shall grant you just one.
A spell that I desire?
I have knowledge of nearly every grimoire
that's ever been written.
Mages spend their entire lives
searching for the spell they desire.
Tell me what yours is,
and I shall grant it to you.
I don't want one.
The greatest joy of magic
lies in searching for it.
Flamme, this girl is no good after all.
She lacks a burning ambition.
Master, someday this girl
will defeat the Demon King.
It will be a mage like her
who clears the way to a peaceful era.
Are you saying I cannot?
As one who seeks battle,
you cannot kill the Demon King.
We can't do it.
After all, you can't imagine yourself
living in a peaceful era, can you?
Frieren is a mage of a peaceful era.
Good answer.
This is how mages ought to be.
Damn it. He won't freeze at all.
The difference between
our mana is too great.
Nephtear.
Weak.
Kanne, defense!
I know!
You two put on quite the show earlier,
so I believe I know most of your tricks.
Relatively non-lethal ice magic,
and a mage who can't fight without water.
What am I even doing here?
This really is just babysitting.
That's not a nice thing to say.
Won't you run out of mana
casting such flashy spells?
You graduated from magic school, didn't you?
Are the old folks still teaching their students
to fight defensive battles of attrition?
What do you mean?
Let me lecture you on the history of magic.
The defensive spell developed to combat
Zoltraak is highly resistant to magic itself,
but its effectiveness against physical
objects has hardly changed since then.
Naturally, there's a clear reason for that.
It's enough to defend against the physical
attacks of monsters and warriors.
Defensive magic mustn't be over-engineered.
If we aimed for perfection,
the technique would become too complex,
which would have a fatal effect
on activation time.
The history of magic is one
of attacking and defending.
It's the reason there's a trend
for modern attack spells
to involve controlling physical objects.
Do you understand what I'm getting at?
Kanne, no! Move!
My spells overwhelm my opponents
with high-volume physical attacks.
Now stay down.
Give me a break.
I'm not interested in hurting you.
Or do you want me to kill you after all?
Should you be approaching us so carelessly?
Sixty percent of the human body
is made of water.
So what?
Magic is a world of visual imagination.
Can you picture how that water is distributed
throughout a person's body,
and how you'd remove and manipulate it?
How would you do that to a mage
protected by a large amount of mana?
Spells can't produce effects
you can't picture.
And even if there were water here,
a small girl like you is no threat to me.
Not even bluffing works?
I hate adults like you.
But I have figured out one thing.
You're lying.
If you loved fighting enough
to lecture us on it,
you would've beaten us
somewhere there was water.
What are you so afraid of?
Behave yourselves.
My job is just to put you two to sleep.
As long as Denken doesn't lose, that is.
At this rate, this battle will end
when she exhausts my mana.
This is all a bit tough for this old body.
My apologies, Frieren, but I'm
going to settle this quickly.
Waldgose.
Daosdorg.
What is that decrepit old man doing?
That old man fights rather spectacularly.
Will the barrier hold?
Of course. The barrier was created
by the great mage Serie.
It cannot be destroyed by brute force.
Oh? That's good, then.
By the way, since around yesterday evening,
someone's been analyzing the barrier.
Why?
I don't know.
In any case, they're wasting their time.
Do you really think there's a mage
in this world greater than Serie?
Catastravia.
Impossible. A counterattack?
That was a continuous volley
of spears of light.
She shouldn't have had the opportunity.
I'm out of mana. So this is the end.
I don't believe it.
She only used basic combat
spells until the end.
This was practically a combat
lesson for a trainee mage.
I'm surprised.
Even at my level, there was
still someone above me.
Tell me where Laufen is.
I know you know.
I'm taking back our Stille.
If you were in my position,
do you think you'd tell me?
You're right.
Laufen, you're hiding nearby, aren't you?
Bring the Stille here.
If you don't, I'll kill Denken.
Don't do it, Laufen.
She doesn't intend to kill me.
You can tell, can't you?
The old man was beaten.
She's a far better mage than me—
no, better than even Richter.
But she underestimates us.
She's not touching the old man's body.
Don't use Jilwer. Stay hidden.
If you release even the slightest bit
of mana, she'll detect you.
From this distance, I could
retrieve the old man and flee!
Don't. It's a trap.
You leave me no choice.
I don't really want to do this, but...
Found you.
You fool.
You inexperienced fool.
You knew she wouldn't kill me.
But she planned to hurt you
without killing you.
We still would've won.
Why are you so desperate
to become a first-class mage?
You've got wealth, influence,
and everything else you could want.
My homeland is located deep
in the Northern Plateau.
Because the demons are acting up, only
first-class mages can enter the area now.
I wanted to visit a grave
I haven't been to in a while.
That's all.
Shouldn't you go help the kids?
Perhaps it's too late, though.
Richter will kill them before he faces you.
He's capable of making pragmatic choices.
They'll be fine. Kanne and Lawine will win.
I just finished analyzing the barrier.
I wasn't expecting Denken to lose.
Now, then.
Babysitting time is over.
He's actually trying to kill us now.
We won't last a minute against him.
Analyzing the barrier?
What do you mean?
Frieren. Don't tell me, you...
Genau.
It's not a problem. It's impossible.
Even if the world were turned upside down—
It's going to break.
Sense, who is that elf mage?
According to the list of test-takers,
her name is Frieren.
That's the name of the mage who
traveled with the party of heroes.
She apparently had a holy emblem, too.
So she's the last great mage.
Now you've done it, Frieren.
It's been a thousand years,
and this is how you say hello?
This is why I can't quit being a mage.
In the world of magic, sometimes
the world is turned upside down.
I can't believe you actually
destroyed the barrier.
Why would you do that?
Because I felt sorry for Kanne.
Magic should be free.
She controls water, does she?
Magic is a world of visual imagination.
Can you imagine defeating a mage
who controls water in the rain?
At the very least, I can't.
I doubt Richter can either.
The barrier...
What happened?
It's raining.
No, I can figure out what happened later.
I have to finish them now—
You finally showed an opening.
Your panic is disrupting your mana.
This will only buy you time!
I see now why you feared a spell
that could control water.
This is the perfect example of the
high-volume physical attacks you mentioned.
Lawine, don't let him get away.
Reamstroha.
There's nowhere for me to run, anyway.
This is why I don't like water.
Looks like you won.
Let's get away from here.
The sun sets in two hours.
You can conceal your mana
until then, can't you?
I don't have any mana left to conceal.
I see. You did well.
Don't pat my head.
Sorry.
It was inevitable.
Denken and I are out of mana.
We have two hours left.
We're finished.
Laufen, can you dispel the binding?
You must be joking.
This binding spell is ridiculously powerful.
Then bring down the tree instead.
Denken, there's nothing we can do.
I don't have the mana left
to use Jilwer anymore.
Richter and Laufen, what do you think
an imperial mage does in this situation?
He keeps fighting until the end.
We'll search for signs of battles fought
by other parties and track them down.
You know, Fern,
you're really rather boring.
You seriously do only cast basic spells.
You should direct your
complaints to Ms. Frieren.
Come to think of it,
that elf is your master, right?
It's her fault we're soaking wet right now.
Make sure you give her an earful, all right?
I intend to.
Also, she doesn't limit what spells
I cast outside of combat.
Come to think of it, you did cast
a spell to catch that bird.
What other spells can you use?
Let's see...
I have a spell that lets you
see through clothes...
I'm not going to cast it.
I hate to interrupt your
pleasant conversation,
but maybe you shouldn't reveal
too many of your tricks.
From the second test onward,
we'll be competing against one another.
You're right.
Sorry 'bout that.
But I think you should've opened up
some more, four-eyes.
There they are.
It's a defeated party.
The corpse of one of their
members was nearby.
Even though there's no way for them to pass,
they're keeping a tight hold on their Stille.
Are we going to negotiate with them, Denken?
They wouldn't cooperate.
If I were in their position,
I'd refuse even money.
Why?
It wouldn't sit right with me.
It's not about logic.
Laufen, wait here.
If you see an opportunity,
take their Stille.
Richter, come with me.
What do you intend to do?
We're approaching them head-on?
We don't have any mana left.
Don't you get it?
They're in the same boat.
Prepare yourself.
You're a man, aren't you?
You're joking, right?
Let's settle this with our fists!
It's time.
The first test is now over.
Six parties—eighteen individuals—
have passed the first test.
The second test will take place
three days from now.
You will be informed of the details later.
That's all. You are dismissed.
It's been two days since
they left for the exam.
I can stay up as late as I want,
and Fern isn't around to get mad at me.
I'm so happy, it's scary.
Sounds like you've got it rough, buddy.
And I'm alright
Yeah, I hear you
The wind teases this hair that's longer now
There's meaning in everything
Even the days that came to a halt
Now that I finally understand,
I've caught up to you
See, things that couldn't have been
Seen if it weren't for these eyes
Why? They begin to overflow
I won't ask to see you, so at least
Let me remember the past, just for today
So, if we were to meet again
No more hesitations, I'd choose the present
Anytime, anywhere, yah
Anytime, anywhere
I'll be there (close your eyes,
and I'll always be there)
Even if there are no absolutes
I'm always aware of your thoughts
Those tears will be alright,
dawn will surely break
I'm whispering our lullaby
for you to come back home
I'm not sharing.
Don't worry, Ms. Frieren.
Don't talk about that.
You're even more spoiled than me.
It's not my birthday.
I can't indulge myself like this.
You must eat your vegetables, too.
This guy is a pain in the butt.
We're no longer party members.
Next time, we'll be enemies.